bigstockphoto.com 2011-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Stock Photos & Vector Art | BIGSTOCK

The practices of SS SPV LLC d/b/a Bigstock (hereinafter "Bigstock"), with respect to personal information, are governed by this Privacy Policy as same may be amended from time to time. Bigstock encourages visitors to and users of **Bigstock.com** (hereinafter referred to as "you" and "users") **** to regularly review this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [privacy@bigstock.com](mailto:privacy@bigstock.com).

## Changes in Privacy Policy

All "personal information" (information that can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that Bigstock collects and maintains is subject to this Privacy Policy. Bigstock reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, in its sole discretion, and will provide notice of any material changes to you. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, changes to the Privacy Policy after such notice has been posted. However, Bigstock will not change any limitation on the use of your personal information selected by you, without your express consent.

In the event that a controlling stake of Bigstock is acquired by, or if Bigstock merges with another entity, Bigstock may provide to such entity your personal information without your consent. Bigstock will provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on the Site.

## Entities collecting personal information

Personal information provided to [www.bigstock.com](http://www.bigstock.com/), and all related, Bigstock and Bigstockphoto branded sites (e.g. bigstockphoto.com, bigstockphoto.de, etc.) is collected by SS SPV LLC d/b/a Bigstock, 60 Broad Street, 30th Floor, New York, NY 10004, USA (Tel. 1-800-631-9809). Bigstock branded sites are collectively referred to herein as the "Site".

## Collection of personal information

**Subscribers**

Visitors to the Site can browse the content available thereon without providing any personal information. However, to license images users must disclose certain personal information to Bigstock.

To give you the most functionality, you may choose to create a "Bigstock Account". Creating a Bigstock Account will enable you to: a) review and amend the personal information you disclose to Bigstock; b) track your Bigstock purchase and download history; and c) use advanced functionality such as lightboxes.

When you create a Bigstock Account, you will be asked to disclose some or all of the following personal information:

  * Contact information such as your name, phone number, mailing address and email address; 
  * Billing information such as the number, expiration date, card type and billing address of your credit card; 
  * Demographic information such as your job title, job description, company name and company type.

You may modify this information by logging in to your Bigstock Account page. Due to security precautions, you may find certain personal information can only be changed by contacting support.

You do not need to create a Bigstock Account to license images from Bigstock. If you choose to use Bigstock's "Guest Checkout" option, you will be required to enter an email address along with that information necessary for Bigstock to process your credit card, including your name, address, and credit card information. Bigstock will store this information, along with reference to the Content purchased, in a "Guest Account". You may access this information by creating a Bigstock Account using the same email address which you used in the Guest Checkout process.

**Contributors**

To submit images to Bigstock for licensing, you will be asked to provide some or all of the following personal information:

  * Contact information such as your name, phone number, mailing address, and email address.
  * Payment and contributor information including, but not limited to, payout method, payout email, desired display name, skill level, content focus, etc.

## How your personal information is used

Bigstock does not share your personal information with third parties in any way other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

Bigstock or one of Bigstock's trusted partners may use your personal information to:

  * Process your financial transactions.
  * Send you order confirmations.
  * Register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users.
  * Respond to customer service requests, questions and concerns.
  * Administer your account.
  * Send you requested product or service information.
  * Keep you informed about special offers and services of Bigstock and selected third parties.
  * Administer promotions and sweepstakes you enter and notify you of the results.
  * Investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities and/or violations of Bigstock's Terms of Service.
  * Meet research and product/service development needs and to improve the Site, services and offerings.
  * Customize your experience, including targeting services and offerings to you.

Bigstock further reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law (e.g., to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or legal process served on Bigstock) and when Bigstock believes that disclosure is necessary to protect Bigstock's rights, avoid litigation, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request. Bigstock may also disclose information about you if Bigstock determines that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.

## Service Providers

Bigstock uses an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. This company is not permitted to retain, share, store or use personal information for any purpose beyond the scope of its services to Bigstock.

In order to reduce errors in Bigstock's database, authenticate users, and prevent abuse of Bigstock's services, Bigstock may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third-party sources. For example, Bigstock may supplement your Personal Information with address information provided by the U.S. Postal Service to qualify your information and prevent errors in Bigstock's database. As permissible, Bigstock may also supplement the information you provide with demographic and other information (such as age or interest in photography) stored in third-party databases in order to make it more likely that marketing communications Bigstock sends you will be of interest.

## Tracking Technologies

Bigstock may use web analytics software. Web analytics software records data such as your mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity, page views, average time spent on the Site, among other things. This data is used to analyze and optimize the Site. Bigstock never uses analytics software to record any personal information entered via this Site nor will the web analytics software track browsing habits across other web sites. You can choose to disable the use of such software as it pertains to your use of the Site by contacting Bigstock at [privacy@bigstock.com](mailto:privacy@bigstock.com).

Bigstock and partners of Bigstock may use cookies and action tags to keep track of your visits, preferences and profile information.

  * A cookie is a small, unique text file that a website can send to your computer when you visit a site. Bigstock may use session cookies, which terminate when a user closes his or her browser, and/or persistent cookies, which remain on the user's computer until manually deleted. Most web browsers can either alert you to the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. If you do not want us to deploy cookies to your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie on your computer. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use the Site.
  * An action tag is similar to a cookie. Action tags help us identify and track the performance of web pages on the Site, allowing us to measure the performance and quality of the Site and to manage Site content. In addition, Bigstock may use action tags in emails. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of marketing campaigns by showing, for example, how many emails have been opened.

Electronic tracking technologies are used to enhance your experience on the Site, including allowing you to remain logged in on the Site. Cookies and pixel tags may also be used to collect general usage and aggregated statistical information that does not identify you personally. However, Bigstock and partners of Bigstock may use cookies to store some of your preferences (including limited Personal Information) or to display relevant content based upon what you view on the Site.

## Your choices with respect to personal information

Bigstock recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible and respectful use of the personal information collected on the Site. You may "opt out" of receiving Bigstock's promotional email updates, newsletters and/or partner emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link available near the bottom of any Bigstock marketing email.

Bigstock reserves the right to contact you when there are changes to the Terms Service, or for other service related announcements as applicable. For instance, if Bigstock's services are temporarily suspended for maintenance, Bigstock may send an email notifying users of same. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option of deactivating your account.

## Protection of your personal information

The security of your personal information is important to us and Bigstock protects it several ways.

  * Access to the personal information on your User Account requires a password. You should use a password that is at least 8 characters long, and comprised of a combination of letters, numbers and symbols. Do not divulge your password to anyone. 
  * Your personal information resides on a password-protected, secure server. Only select Bigstock personnel and contractors who require access to do their job are given the password to the server. 
  * Bigstock encrypts your personal information during transmission to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to and from Bigstock. 
  * When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on registration or order forms, Bigstock encrypts that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Bigstock strives to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once Bigstock receives it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While Bigstock uses commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Bigstock cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on the Site, you can send email to us on Bigstock's Contact Us page.

## Privacy complaints

Bigstock takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Bigstock has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may contact the General Counsel at Bigstock, 60 Broad Street, 30th Floor, New York, NY 10004, USA. In your letter please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Bigstock Privacy Policy has not been complied with.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Bigstock on the Contact Us page.

Effective November 3, 2011
